"There are too many adventurers." "I don't like the smell on them."
"冒險者太多 他們身上的味道我不是很喜歡"
"The tourists litter."
"觀光客老是亂丟垃圾"
"Please build a theatre."
"希望能建個劇場"
"Please build more roads."
"希望能修建道路"
"Please station knights in Avancier."
"希望騎士也可以進駐阿凡錫亞"
These are the requests of the town residents.
以上是鎮上居民主要的要求
There are more besides those.
除此之外 還有其他願望
Please go through them, Big Brother.
還請你過目一下喔 哥哥
I'll go clean up.
那我先去打掃環境了
Lime,
萊伊姆
let's race to the second floor!
我們來比誰先跑到二樓吧
The sound of Manicia running energetically up the stairs
瑪妮西婭充滿活力地 在樓梯上奔跑的聲音
is truly wonderful.
真是太美妙了
Still,
話說回來
I didn't expect to receive so many petitions.
居然有這麼多請願書
I'm glad we formed an alliance with the two major clans,
雖然很慶幸很兩大戰團結盟
but even problems can arise from such rapid development.
但發展得太好 也有各種煩惱呢
Rud, come with me!
路德 跟我過來一下
Nin? What's wrong?
妮恩 妳怎麼了？
This way!
過來這裡
This girl collapsed on the road.
有個女孩子倒在路上
She's a Homunculus.
這孩子 是人造人
Please… Please help us!
請…請妳救救我們
I have friends!
我還有其他同伴
We were attacked in the forest nearby!
但我們在附近的森林裡遭到攻擊
Let's go.
我們快過去吧
Yes.
好
Master,
主人
I'll go too.
我也要一起去
No, you need to stay here, Luna.
不 露娜妳留在這裡
You treated her injuries.
畢竟是妳幫她療好傷的
She'll feel safer with you here.
妳待在這裡她也會比較安心吧
I understand.
我知道了
THE STRONGEST TANK'S LABYRINTH RAIDS
《最強肉盾的迷宮攻略～擁有稀少技能體力9999的肉盾，被勇者隊伍辭退了～》
Around the labyrinth?
是在迷宮那邊嗎
But I'm the one managing the labyrinth right now.
但迷宮現在是我在管理的
There shouldn't be monsters spawning outside.
應該不會有魔物跑出來才對
Found them.
找到他們了
The Homunculi are fighting each other!
人造人…在互相廝殺
One side's clearly at a disadvantage.
有一方明顯處於弱勢呢
And the side that's under attack
而且被襲擊的那一方
clearly has emotions like the girl we found.
似乎都跟剛才那女孩一樣擁有情感
I am an adventurer from a nearby town called Avancier.
我是來自附近一個 叫阿凡錫亞的城鎮的冒險者
Please listen to what I have to say.
請你們聽我說一下
Please.
拜託了
It's not working.
行不通嗎
Your friend came to our town and asked me to help you.
是你們的同伴來到我們鎮上 請我幫助你們的
That girl's abilities are on par with the pursuers.
那女孩的能力和追兵不相上下嗎
You must be the Homunculi she meant.
你們就是那些人造人吧
Yes, it's us.
沒錯 就是我們
So, who are these?
那麼 這些人又是誰？
They are combat-type Homunculi from Brunn Quelez.
他們是"布倫凱斯國"的 戰鬥型人造人
Brunn Quelez?
布倫凱斯國
Luna escaped from that country.
露娜就是從那個國家逃過來的
In other words,
也就是說
these are illegally created Homunculi.
他們是違法製造的人造人吧
Nin,
妮恩
heal them.
麻煩妳幫他們治療一下
On it.
好
"Area High Heal"!
"大範圍治療"
I was wondering what all the ruckus was about.
還想說怎麼吵吵鬧鬧的
It appears things have gotten a bit tricky.
事情變得有些麻煩了呢
It's only natural that they would feel uneasy.
他們會感到不安也是理所當然的
After all, something that should have been forbidden
畢竟本該被禁止製造的東西 竟然突然出現在自己面前
So even though they're combat-type Homunculi,
所以他們雖然是戰鬥型人造人
they don't possess emotions or consciousness
但卻跟你們不一樣
like you guys do?
沒有感情或自我意識嗎
That's right.
是的
They're only after us to complete the order
他們追過來只是為了達成
to exterminate all those who escaped.
"殺死我們這些逃跑者" 這個目的而已
I see.
這樣啊
That means we'll have to defeat them.
看來得打倒他們才行了
Although they're Homunculi…
但是 雖說對方是人造人…
No, it's precisely so that I can't bring myself to do it.
不 應該說正因如此 才讓我難以下手
Because they might be able
畢竟他們也可能像露娜那般
to laugh or cry like Luna...
天真地笑著 或是放聲大哭
Can't you bring yourself to do it?
你下不了手嗎
Amos.
亞蒙
In the end, they are merely puppets
那些傢伙說到底 其實跟人偶沒兩樣
bestowed a semblance of life.
不過是一些被賦予了 類似生命的存在罷了
Her words are cold,
雖然說出口的話很冷漠
but she must have said them for my peace of mind.
但她應該是在顧慮我的感受吧
Their movements don't seem very swift.
他們的動作似乎沒有很快
They can still attack even after losing a limb.
沒想到就算被砍下手臂 他們還能繼續攻擊
This is indeed something only a Homunculus could do.
這確實是人造人才能做出的攻擊呢
I won't be able to block it in time.
這樣下去會來不及擋下攻擊的
It's different from before.
跟當時不一樣
Is it because I still have my shield force?
是因為現在有護盾嗎
I feel much lighter than usual.
感覺身體比平時還輕盈許多
Finally, it's over.
終於結束了嗎
Rud, I've healed them.
路德 我幫他們治療好了
Um,
那個
your friend is in something like a house of ours.
你們的同伴在一個 類似我家的地方
Will you come too?
你們要一起來嗎
Some look uneasy,
有人面露不安
while others are filled with hostility.
也有人充滿敵意
They really are quite different.
還真是各有不同呢
But we can't force them.
但也不能勉強他們
The way they're dressed,
從他們的打扮看來
they must've been treated very inhumanely.
過去應該過著十分不人道的生活
It's likely they hate humans too.
搞不好他們不喜歡人類
Um...
那個
If you'll let us,
如果可以的話
can we come with you?
能讓我們跟你一起走嗎
Honestly, I'm not the biggest fan of humans.
老實說 我並不喜歡人類
But some of us are wounded,
但我們這邊還有傷者
and we have nowhere else to go.
而且我們也無處可去了
We brought the Homunculi we rescued
順利救出人造人們的我們
to the clan house.
把他們帶回了戰團的宅邸
That settles it for now.
總之 算是暫且告一段落了
We can protect them here,
不過 我們雖然可以保護他們
but what do you plan to do next?
但你今後有什麼打算？
They're Homunculi from Brunn Quelez.
既然他們是布倫凱斯國的人造人
Then we must inform the governor at the lord's mansion.
那我們就必須 跟領主宅邸的官員大人說吧
The information will reach the upper echelons of the country.
如此一來 就會傳到國家的上層去
If that happens, we might not be able to protect them.
這樣可沒辦法保護他們喔
And the townsfolk might also be wary of them.
而且鎮上的人 或許也會提防他們
I know.
我知道
-Fortunately, the governor in Avancier -You can stay here
-幸好阿凡錫亞的官員大人比較親切 -你們放心待在這裡吧
He will hear us out, at the very least.
他應該會先聽看看我們的意見吧
Um...
那個
Thank you for helping us.
剛才很謝謝你
My name is Fia.
我叫做菲亞
Are you going to meet with the local authorities?
你接下來要去見這裡的大官嗎
Yes.
沒錯
Can I come with you?
那麼 我也可以一起去嗎
It might be easier for a party involved to speak to them.
讓當事人直接跟他們說會比較快吧
They probably want to know about the situation in Brunn Quelez too.
而且那些大官應該也想知道 布倫凱斯國的狀況吧
But they might be cautious of you.
但是 他們可能會對妳有所戒備喔
Well, you can tie up my hands and feet.
那麼 你可以把我的手腳都綁起來
I'm not one not to repay my debts.
我可不是那種得到幫助 卻不給予任何回報的人喔
I'll tell you everything
我會把我可以說的事情
I can.
全部告訴你們的
I see.
我知道了
But there's no need to tie up your hands and feet.
不過 沒必要綁住妳的手腳喔
In that case...
那麼…
I've never seen her before.
是沒看過的人呢
I heard a group of people with magic stones on them were brought to the clan house.
聽說有一群人身上有魔石的人 被帶到戰團宅邸了
Mr. Rud lead them there.
路德先生帶來的人
Are they Homunculi?
該不會是人造人吧
Is this really all right?
這樣沒問題嗎
Um, Rud...
那個 路德
Yes?
怎麼了？
I asked you to hold my hand as a safety precaution,
雖然是為了"拘束行動" 才請你牽著我的手
but we've certainly attracted a lot of attention.
但這樣果然很引人注目呢
I apologise
要是給你添麻煩
for any inconveniences caused.
只能先跟你說聲抱歉了
I don't think that at all.
妳沒有給我添麻煩喔
I'm the one who should apologise.
不如說 我才要跟妳說聲抱歉
The people of Avancier have never seen a Homunculus.
因為阿凡錫亞的人 沒見過你們這樣的人造人
But they don't mean any ill intent.
但大家其實沒有惡意
It's okay. I don't mind.
沒事的 我不介意喔
We were prepared
因為我們是做好各種覺悟
before we left that country.
才離開那個國家的
I see.
這樣啊
Also,
還有
you don't have to force yourself to smile.
妳其實不需要強顏歡笑喔
At least not when you're with me.
至少在我的面前不需要
I see. I understand what happened.
這樣啊 我瞭解事情經過了
It's been hard on you, Fia.
之前辛苦你們了呢 菲亞
So that country is creating Homunculi.
不過 那個國家果然在製造人造人啊
Were you already aware of this, sir?
官員 您早就知道這件事了嗎
Only rumours.
雖然只是有所耳聞而已
I hear they do not treat the Homunculi kindly.
不過聽說他們經常會虐待人造人
Can I shelter them in this town to protect them?
那我今後可以讓他們留在鎮上 保護他們嗎
To protect them?
在鎮上保護他們？
Of course,
當然
them having nowhere else to go is one of the reasons.
雖說是因為他們無處可去
But more importantly, if they stay,
不過最重要的是 如果他們願意留在這裡
they may solve the problem of the lack of manpower.
或許就能解決人手不足的問題了
Are you planning to hire the Homunculi?
難道 你是想雇用人造人嗎
Precisely.
是的
They possess their own will
因為他們擁有自我意識
and can act accordingly.
可以根據自己的想法做出行動
You make a fair point.
好吧 你說的有道理
I could tell just by looking at this child.
光看這孩子 我就知道了
They're nothing different from humans,
他們和"人類"沒什麼差別
and they're very expressive.
而且表情也很豐富呢
Well then, Fia,
那麼 菲亞
I have some questions for you.
我有事想問妳
When it comes to the Homunculi,
所謂的人造人 有你們這種…
Commander-type with thinking ability and self-awareness
"擁有思考能力和自我意識的指揮型"
and combat-type with enhanced combat skills.
以及"強化戰鬥能力的戰鬥型"
Besides these, there seem to be various types of Homunculi.
除此之外 似乎還有各式各樣的人造人
By chance do you know the reason
那妳知道人造人技術 為什麼會發展得這麼迅速嗎
Well,
這個嘛
it's said that about 20 years ago,
據說是因為大約20年前
a man known as Demon Lord Greed appeared in Brunn Quelez.
布倫凱斯國內出現了一位 名叫魔王葛利德的男人
A demon lord?
魔王？
We all thought demon lords were fictional.
我們都以為魔王是虛構的存在
Why would he appear in Brunn Quelez?
他為什麼會出現在布倫凱斯呢
I don't know the exact reason,
我也不知道明確的原因
but it seems
但是
that the remarkable development of Homunculus technology
好像確實是因為魔王葛利德
is indeed attributed to Demon Lord Greed.
才讓人造人技術有了卓越的發展
Even now, they continue to mass-produce Homunculi like us.
就連現在 他們也在不斷量產 我們這樣的人造人
I understand the general situation.
我知道大致情況了
I'll convey this information to higher-ups.
我會把剛才那些情報轉達上去
Furthermore,
此外
we will provide your group protection in Avancier.
我也會讓你們留在阿凡錫亞 接受保護
Thank you very much!
謝謝您
Looks like we get to stay in town for the time being.
看來能暫時留在鎮上了呢
Yes.
是啊
But in a way you guys are also being monitored.
只是說到底 也算變相地監視你們就是了
I understand.
我知道
By the way,
對了
wasn't there a girl back in the forest
剛才在森林裡
who could hold her own against a combat-type Homunculus?
不是有個女孩可以 和戰鬥型人造人打得不相上下嗎
Saminina?
你是說薩米彌娜嗎
She's pretty tough for a commander-type Homunculus.
她在指揮型人造人中 確實算身手矯健
If anything were to happen, she could be a formidable force.
萬一日後發生什麼事 她應該可以成為一大戰力
She's not the friendliest,
雖然個性不是很親切
but she genuinely cares for her friends.
但她其實是個 很為同伴著想的孩子喔
I can see that.
這一點 我好像感覺得出來
CHUCKLE
(竊笑)
Some of our kind resents humans
因為我們過去受到 許多慘無人道的對待
because of the horrors we've suffered in the past.
所以有些人很痛恨人類
But you helped us and let us know
但是 你幫助了我們
that there are human beings out there who will treat Homunculi kindly.
讓我們知道人類當中 也有人會溫柔地對待人造人
Those of you who have followed us here should have realised that.
那些跟來這裡的同伴應該都發現這一點了
So,
所以
even though they might not let their guard down immediately,
雖然可能沒辦法馬上放下心防
everyone will surely understand one day.
但大家總有一天 肯定都會明白的
That's true.
說得也是
What can I do
為了讓他們能正常生活
to help them integrate into the life here?
我可以為他們做些什麼呢？
That's the situation.
事情就是這樣
All of you will be allowed to stay in town for protection.
目前已經正式確定 可以讓你們留在鎮上接受保護了
So
所以
I'm hoping you can do something to help the town.
我希望你們可以幫鎮上做些什麼
Can you tell me what you're good at?
可以告訴我 你們擅長的事嗎
I'm not sure if we're good at it,
雖然不確定算不算擅長
but in Brunn Quelez,
但我們在布倫凱斯
we are responsible for making clothes, weapons,
都負責製作服裝和武器
or building facilities that are insufficient.
或蓋一些不夠用的設施
We have also built towns.
也有蓋過城鎮喔
That's very impressive.
好厲害喔
It seems you guys are skilled in many things.
看來你們做什麼都很優秀呢
But Saminina's better at fighting than making things.
不過薩米彌娜比起製造東西 更擅長戰鬥呢
No... I don't want to work.
不要 我不要工作
We'll be abused again.
又會被虐待的
They'll beat us with whips.
他們會拿鞭子打我們
I don't want to work for humans.
我不想在人類手下工作
I almost forgot
差點忘了
that they used to work under terrible conditions.
他們過去都是在非常惡劣的 環境下工作
I have to quell their anxieties first.
應該先消除他們內心的不安才對
It's work,
雖說是工作
but never more than a reasonable number of hours.
但工作時數絕對不會超過合理範圍
How long is that?
那樣是多久啊？
Normally, it should be from 9 AM to 6 PM.
基本上應該是 早上9點到晚上6點吧
You'll be given breaks as well, of course.
當然 也有休息時間喔
That's…
好…
So short!
好短
I can't believe it!
真是不敢置信
-We even get breaks? -We won't be yelled at, will we?
-還可以休息嗎 -不會跑來罵我們吧
It seems their previous working environment was really harsh.
看來他們之前的 工作環境真的很惡劣呢
We'll decide the details of the job and the hours later.
詳細的工作內容和時間 我們之後再慢慢決定
Anyway, thank you all very much.
總之 真的很謝謝大家
What's wrong?
怎麼了嗎
It's just that...
不是 那個…
People don't thank the Homunculi,
因為沒有人會跟人造人道謝
so that was a little surprising.
所以我覺得有些震驚
I see.
這樣啊
Work for the Homunculi?
人造人們的工作內容嗎
In that case, how about this?
那麼 你們覺得這個怎麼樣呢？
We'll build a public bathhouse.
蓋一個公共澡堂
Sounds good.
感覺不錯呢
We've gotten requests for a theatre and more guards too,
雖然也有人提出 蓋劇場或護衛的要求
but a public bathhouse might be better.
但先蓋澡堂或許比較好呢
Those adventurers could certainly use it.
冒險者的那個 確實讓人挺討厭的呢
Some of them are rather unhygienic...
畢竟也有一些不愛洗澡的傢伙啊
The public bathhouse it is, then.
那就決定蓋公共澡堂了
Manicia,
瑪妮西婭
could I have you write up the proposal to the governor?
可以麻煩妳寫 要提交給官員的企劃書嗎
Certainly.
好的
By the way,
話說回來
don't you think Luna's been acting a little strange lately?
你不覺得露娜最近有點怪怪的嗎
Has she?
有嗎
Yes.
有啊
Can I stay with the Homunculi
從今天起 我可以暫時…
at the clan house for a while?
和人造人們一起住在戰團的宅邸嗎
She seemed very concerned about the Homunculi.
她不是一直很在意人造人他們嗎
She didn't leave the second floor today.
今天也完全沒有離開二樓
Does she have some sort of attachment towards the Homunculi?
她是不是對人造人 抱有什麼特殊的情感呀
Luna.
露娜
Master.
主人
Let me give you a hand.
我來幫妳吧
Did something happen?
請問發生什麼事了嗎
Hmm, well, how should I put it?
嗯 那個 該怎麼說呢
I have something to tell you.
我有些話想跟妳說
Since the Homunculi came to Avancier,
自從人造人來到阿凡錫亞
you've been quite busy.
妳不是一直很忙嗎
So, I was thinking, um...
所以我想說 那個…
It might be good for us to have a chat once in a while.
偶爾撥空聊聊天 或許也挺不錯的
Of course.
好的
Although it's been decided to build a public bathhouse,
雖然現在決定要蓋公共澡堂了
can they still stay here
但是蓋好後
once it's finished?
他們還可以留在這裡嗎
Will they be dismissed
會不會等蓋好後
after it's done?
就不要他們了呢
Don't worry.
別擔心
The higher-ups have already decided to leave me in charge of everything.
這部分上頭已經決定 全權交由我負責了
I see.
這樣啊
Luna, are you okay?
倒是露娜 妳沒事吧？
You've been spending a lot of time with the Homunculi lately.
妳最近總是和人造人待在一起
It seems you've also heard about what happened in Brunn Quelez.
似乎也聽說了不少 他們在布倫凱斯國發生的事
Yes.
是啊
I feel so grateful and fortunate
我最近深刻地覺得 自己能被主人帶回來
to be brought back by Master.
真是的一件非常幸運的事
Maybe Luna doesn't remember much about life in that country.
或許露娜不太記得 在那邊生活時的事了
That's why it was quite a shock to her when she learned
所以聽到人造人的經歷
what happened to the other Homunculi.
才會大受打擊吧
Speaking of which,
話說回來
have you told them
妳有跟他們說了嗎
that you're a Homunculus?
說妳也是人造人
No, I haven't told any of them.
沒有 我沒和任何人說過
If I told them,
因為如果告訴他們
it might cause you trouble.
可能會給主人添麻煩
I see.
原來如此
I keep missing the timing to tell them as well.
我也沒想到會一直 找不到時機告訴大家
It'd be better if we could tell them soon.
要是能早點向大家坦白就好了
Yes.
是啊
But...
不過
someday, when the people in town aren't afraid of the Homunculi anymore,
等哪天鎮上的人不再害怕人造人時
I'll tell them my real identity.
我想告訴他們 我的真實身分
I want them to live happily as soon as possible,
為此 我想讓他們盡快變幸福
so I will do my best.
我一定會好好努力的
Mm. Everything will work out.
嗯 絕對不會有問題的
I know you can do it.
如果是妳 肯定辦得到喔
I'm really glad
我也由衷地覺得
I helped you.
當初有幫助妳 真是太好了
Master...
主人
Thank you very much.
真的很謝謝您
In order to the solve the problem faced by Luna and the other Homunculi,
為了解決露娜和菲亞他們的問題
there is something I must find out.
我必須問清楚一件事才行
And who are you looking for?
你在找誰呀？
Amos, just the one I was looking for…
亞蒙 我正好在找妳…
Rud!
路德
Did you make this long journey just to find me?
你是特地跑到這種地方來找我的嗎
Have I completely captivated you?
難道你已經被我迷得神魂顛倒了嗎
Hey! Don't cling to me!
喂 妳別黏在我身上
Ouch…
好痛…
Hey! Rud!
喂 路德
How can I be a role model for my students if they see me in this state?
萬一被學生們看到 我要怎麼做他們榜樣啊
Students?
學生？
I've started teaching magic.
我開了一間魔法教室
After all, I have a lot of free time on my hands.
畢竟我現在很閒啊
Meanwhile, things are hectic on my end.
我這邊倒是忙得不得了呢
We could really use extra help for the construction.
尤其是現在很缺建設相關的人手
Let the Homunculi handle that kind of work.
那種工作讓人造人去做就好
I only do things that interest me.
我這個人只做自己覺得有趣的事
I want them all to learn magic from the demon lord herself,
我要讓大家學習魔王傳授的魔法
so they can all be future candidates for demon lords.
這樣大家之後就都是魔王候補了
That's right.
對了
I came to ask you about demon lords.
我來找妳是為了問 "魔王"相關的事
About me?
要問我的事？
No, about Demon Lord Greed.
不 是關於魔王葛利德的事
Apparently, it was him who brought the Homunculi technology to Brunn Quelez.
聽說傳授布倫凱斯國 人造人技術的就是魔王葛利德
That bloke has always had a penchant for research.
那傢伙確實 從以前就很喜歡研究東西
Even if he knows a thing or two about Homunculus technology,
就算他知道人造人技術
it's nothing surprising.
也沒什麼好奇怪的
Heard he's currently mass-producing Homunculi.
聽說他現在也在量產人造人
Do you know what his purpose is?
妳知道他的目的是什麼嗎
Like, is he planning on invading other countries or something?
比如侵略其他國家之類的
He is probably the last person
唯獨那傢伙
who would consider such intentions.
應該不會有那種打算吧
Then why is he mass-producing Homunculi?
那他幹嘛量產人造人？
Probably just to pass the time.
應該是用來打發時間吧
Just to pass the time?
打發時間…嗎
Well, us demon lords aren't exactly restricted by a lifespan.
畢竟我們這些魔王不會受壽命限制
Even if we die,
就算死掉了
one day we'll resurrect in the same manner.
有天也會以同樣的姿態再次復活
Immortal, some might say.
就像不老不死一樣
I've heard that when you die, you lose your memories
只是聽說死掉後 就會失去記憶
and come back to life somewhere else.
然後在某個地方重新復活
Although some can vaguely recall their past memories,
雖然也有人 能依稀回想起過去的記憶
most forget everything and simply live on.
但大部分都會忘記一切 就那樣生活下去
That's how it is.
總之就是這樣
Since we demon lords don't die,
因為我們這些魔王不會死
we look for matters to occupy our time.
所以會去尋找一些 可以投入精力打發時間的事
So, manufacturing Homunculi is Greed's pastime
所以製造人造人
to while away his lengthy existence?
就是葛利德用來度過 漫長人生的消遣活動嗎
Not exactly.
那倒不是
Greed has always sought to create "the strongest".
葛利德一直在研究 "最強的製作方法"
His research of the Homunculi is most likely
所以人造人的研究
one of his many studies.
只是其中一個候補選項罷了
To create the strongest?
最強的製作方法？
I suppose
這樣聽下來
the illegal Homunculi are the closest to being the "strongest".
違法人造人 確實最接近"最強"的概念呢
You're one to talk, being the closest to "strongest".
最接近"最強"的你 好意思這麼說嗎
The power you possess is something
你擁有的力量
that even Greed, after years of research, cannot obtain.
就是葛利德經過長年的研究 仍然無法得到的東西
Mana, strengthened by the power of the demon lord.
透過名為魔王之力的魔力得到強化
Shield force, enhanced by the power of god.
透過名為神之力的護盾得到強化
Possess both, and only then does one become the strongest.
同時擁有這兩種能力 才是所謂的"最強"
This is the conclusion that Greed has reached through research.
這就是葛利德經過研究得出的結論
Didn't you use it when you fought me?
你之前和我對戰時 不是有用過嗎
The power at that time?
妳是指當時那股力量嗎
Now I understand that Greed is pursuing the "strongest".
現在我知道葛利德 在追求"最強"的力量了
But why create the Homunculi?
但他為什麼會跑去製造人造人呢
Most probably to experiment on their bodies.
應該是想用人造人的肉體 去進行那個實驗吧
So, he created Luna and all those Homunculi
所以他製造出露娜和那些人造人
just to use them as his test subjects?
就只是為了把他們 當作自己的實驗台嗎
He put them
就為了做實驗
through all that suffering just for his research?
害他們過得那麼辛苦嗎
You've got to be kidding me!
開什麼玩笑
Are you angry?
你在生氣嗎
Of course, I am!
當然會生氣啊
Those kids have feelings.
那些孩子都擁有情感
How can I overlook the atrocities he committed?
看到他們遭受那種非人道的對待 我怎麼可能原諒他
What labyrinth is Greed in now?
那個葛利德 現在在哪個迷宮？
What? Are you going to take him down?
怎麼？你打算去打倒他嗎
He's a very powerful man.
那傢伙可是很厲害的喔
With your current strength,
以你現在的力量
you might not be able to defeat Greed at all his might.
或許贏不過認真起來的葛利德
And even if
而且
you do want to defeat him, your "strongest" power can be troublesome.
就算你想打贏他 你擁有的"最強之力"也有點棘手
Magic elements come from monsters.
魔素是從魔物身上流出來的
Used excessively,
一旦過度使用
one's body could become closer to that of a demon.
身體可能會越來越接近"魔之人"
Are you telling me to avoid using it?
所以妳是要我盡量別使用嗎
You should learn to control it.
是要學會控制
Those who cannot control mana will become monsters.
沒辦法控制魔力的人 就會變成魔物
However,
不過
control it well
如果你控制得當
and you might just turn into a demon lord.
也有可能會變成魔王喔
I have no interest
成為魔王什麼的
in becoming a demon lord.
我對那種事一點興趣都沒有
I see.
這樣啊
Well, it's almost time for my lesson.
那麼 差不多到 魔法教室的上課時間了
Let's talk another day, Rud.
改天再聊吧 路德
In order to protect everyone when Greed attacks,
為了哪天葛利德攻過來時 可以保護大家
I have to become stronger.
我要得變得更厲害才行
Destroy it.
破壞掉吧